Yes, sir.
Escoxenzuela.
I really want to hear this.
Yes, sir.
Let me find it.
Hey, do you have two?
Yes, you have two.
One time. Yes, I want to hear it.
Yes, I have a collection.
Yes.
No, I don't have that.
No, no, no, no.
I think I can go a little bit.
I think I can make it.
Ha-ha-ha.
That's not good.
The ad is a little long.
Please wait 5 more seconds
Sweets.
Sweets!
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Isn't this normal?
Aww.
No.
You're kidding.
The first island wins.
No way!
Yes! Yes!
Yes, sir.
Yes, I know, right?
Am I not good enough?
Yes.
Yes. - Yes.
Are you sure?
I'm definitely good at this.
No, no, no, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
We ended up saying that Yuzu was good in front of Yasko.
Yes, he was.
He was definitely good.
Isn't he on right now?
Didn't you see it?
Yes, I did.
Yes, sir.
Yes. - Yes.
What is it?
It's Moka.
It's Moeka.
It's me.
Are you free later tonight?
Would you go out with me?
I've always wanted to talk to Kay.
Even after the rain, we're still having a chat.
Let's go!
Let's talk while it's raining!
Ame-shaberashi-shaberu for short!
Good evening to all of you who are watching our official YouTube Live Ame-shaberashi channel!
Good evening.
We are
We are Ame-shitsureshi.
Please have a good evening.
And now for the title call.
Yuzu is in charge of the title call this time.
Yes, Mr. Kay has recently started to promote Amezurashi.
I was so happy to hear her read the first spacha of her life!
By the way, I'd love to see him live, but it's fun just to talk to him all the time.
I'm glad to hear that it's fun just to talk with him all the time.
I'm so happy!
Aren't you super happy? What's more...
It's the first time in my life that I'm going to see Spacha with Raindrops.
I've been pushing for it lately.
I'm so happy.
And when you say you like the way I talk, you're telling the truth.
She likes the way we talk.
He's our voice.
She's mobilizing us.
Because, you know...
There aren't too many people who say, "That wasn't right.
I'm often told that I'm a little different when I talk.
I'm glad to hear that.
Thank you very much.
Don't put it in sober.
Don't let me in sober.
Let it in, let it in, let it in.
Spacha, are you ready? Okay, then.
Oh, yes!
Here you go.Here you go.
Oh no!
Yaekage's new Starbucks product to be released on the 31st.
Setouchi Setouchi Lemon Frappuccino
Oh no!
Like the Setouchi Sea
oh no!
Enjoy the Setouchi Lemon Frappuccino!
Yes, ma'am!
Wait a minute, how long are you messing with your bangs?
I'm sorry.
It's glossy today.
I don't like it here.
You know what I mean?
I don't know.
It's so bad in here today.
I want to spend another hour here.
Yaekage, enjoy your lemon Frappuccino.
Thank you.
I was really curious about this place.
It was raining today.
Will you shut up for a minute?
How long are you wearing lipstick?
It was raining today.
But it rained a little bit.
So you didn't bring an umbrella.
Yes, I did.
That's why I didn't bring an umbrella.
It was pouring when I got off the train.
I thought, "Oh, my God.
I came to your hair, and the windows are all wet.
Whatever.
Okay, I'll do Spacher.
Nao-san and Namie were a lot of fun.
Thank you very much.
Next, YTXZ Shippo's feeling.
That's nice.
It's the change of season.
I know you're busy.
Take care of yourself.
What? Where is it written?
It sounds very, very difficult.
Please put on your sky hugs.
I'd like to listen to the Sora Sashimi.
But...
Mushi?
Mushi? Mushi?
Sora-hagashi?
What's a sky hug?
Sora-hug
Sora Hug
A menu?
No, the menu?
Do you know what a "takuhagu" is?
It means "taku in the sky" in Japanese.
Sora ni taku.
I knew it! AmeFlash is not good with complicated words.
But I already know that he wants us to be happy.
I already know that.
I see... I get it.
Careful with that. Oh, you taught me that one.
Oh, Karami? Thank you.
I'm sorry. I dug too deep. I'm sorry.
Thank you. That's very kind of you.
The plate is just right. It's right.
It's right? Who's wrong?
It's Moehana. Moehana. I'm sorry.
Next, Mr. Toy, Namie had a good time. May the typhoon go away.
He said he'll make a teru teru bozu so the typhoon will go away. That's great. Thank you.
And now Momotaro says he's seen you for the first time.
I'm so happy!
Aren't there a lot of them? Really?
450, but... there were a lot last time, too.
Yeah, there were a lot. The number of subscribers is up overall.
It was like I saw it, too, but I really saw it.
No, you didn't. I found the first choco choco.
Choco choco, right? Choco choco.
It's a title code.
This is the cat's name caller.
I'm going to pick one of you who tweeted me your thoughts on Ameshabe.
We'll choose one person from among those who tweeted their impressions of Ameshabe and call that person's name.
So please tweet a lot with the hashtag "Ameshabe".
Please tweet a lot with the hashtag Meshabe.
Yesterday, as part of Namie Girls' First Union...
Yesterday we held Namie Girls' First Performance "With You Again" as Namie Girls' First Association.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Some of you may have never seen Namie before, but you don't know what Namie is.
That's right. What is Namie?
Namie is a group of seven.
Like candy flashes.
Naitorna and Kana Haruma. They're from the same office.
And his senior, Momochiro Clover Z.
Arline and I are a seven member group.
We originally started with Nitruna and Kana Haruma's
Hari-chan and Rumpin used to work together.
We split up once, but we're back together again now.
We've been good friends for a long time.
We've been friends for a long time, but we're here to support the recovery of Namie-cho in Fukushima Prefecture.
The group was rescued.The group was rescued.
We're going to Namie-cho, and we're going to do a live concert, and we're going to help out in various ways, and...
But today, we didn't perform in Namie-cho, we performed in Shibuya.
We did Easter in Shibuya.
We did! Some people saw us on TikTok and became our fans.
That's great! Thank you so much!
Yesterday was a lot of fun, wasn't it?
The first thing I noticed was the new costumes!
There were 7 of us in the new costumes and 8 of us in the new costumes.
It was the first solo show with 7 members.
Why the new costumes? They were different from the previous ones.
Like white and light blue.
It was super cute. Like emerald or marble.
Namie's costumes used to be long skirts.
But this time, she's wearing shorts.
The flutters are just like that.
She has several cell phones, right?
Four phones, I think.
There are so many different cell phones.
Miyako's reaction when she saw this new outfit was amazing.
She kept saying, "Wow, it's so cute, I'm so happy to wear it.
I'm so happy. She wants to wear the IA costume.
"I want to wear the IA costume.
It's so cute and looks great on everyone!
This is the most suitable costume for all the members, in Arline's opinion.
I made it with that in mind.
So Aaryn does the costumes too?
Yes, yes. Arline asks me what I want them to look like.
And he also does the singing.
I see, so you do everything.
I'm a PVP.
On the contrary, I'd like to hear which ones don't suit you.
He said the early pink costumes didn't look good on the flowers. Arline.
That's right. That's why I wanted to make sure that even Hana would look good in the costumes this time.
He said they made the costumes so that they would look good on everyone.
So you made me aware of it.
I'm sorry. I'm such a guy.
But it was really cute, and I think this outfit was my favorite.
It's so cute, isn't it?
I love Meguri.
The ribbon was so sparkly.
It was so cute.
It was the most fluttery outfit.
There are many choreographs that are danced in a ska-like way,
It was the easiest to hold and dance with.
It was cute, and I think everyone went "wow".
The hair ornament was cute too.
The first pink costume had matching hair ornaments.
The second one didn't have any hair ornaments,
This time, everyone had different hair ornaments. I told them that they could all wear the same hair ornament.
There were so many hair ornaments that each girl didn't have a specific one,
We had a lot of hair ornaments, and we let them decide freely according to their moods that day,
There were a few people who left after the first and second sessions.
It was really cute.
Then, we came out for the over-challenge,
The first song was a new song. It was "Sakura Nagashi," wasn't it?
That's right.
There was a new song.
Yes, there was a new song. It's a new song,
This is our first song as a seven-member band,
This is the first new song since we became 8 or 7 members,
The lyrics are also very interesting,
I wonder what we could have left behind,
The lyrics are easy to remember, and the melody is easy to remember.
I was just now being crushed by the flowers.
We were talking about the new song.
So, can I have a word now?
We were just talking about the new song.
You're being so noisy.
It's important right now.
I was listening carefully to him talking about his new song.
While I was listening, he made eye contact with me,
That's cute.
No, you're not.
He's wearing Ira's glasses, and he's looking at me, and he's coming at me.
I can't even go to the wrong reaction opinion.
I'm sorry. It's simply too loud.
I don't have that kind of voice.
It's simply too loud.
Can I ask you to hold it?
I dropped it.
I don't like nice things to say.
We were talking nice, weren't we?
Yes, we were.
Seriously, we were talking about the food.
You were starting with the new song, new clothes.
I was getting kind of angry,
You should be careful next to me.
Take a step toward me.
Not in the eye.
Just the edge of the room, so it stretches out.
It's too loud, really.
I'm a bad paperboy.
Please don't do that. My mom at home has started calling me paperhand lousy lately.
You're a bad paper hand, aren't you?
Even when the neighbor's flowers stayed over, my mom is a paperhand.
You're lying.
Mom.
You've all read it.
Kojima is the paper hand and Ichikawa is the shite hand.
Paper hand and paper hand.Mr. Paper Hand and Mr. Underhand.
I don't care what you say about paper hand and underhand.
It's a new song now, right?
Sakura Nagashi.
Center, sorry.
Next to the center.
I hate it the most.
Please, someone who happens to be next to the center by chance.
Thank you very much.
What is it, already?
Okay, please talk already.
Yesterday, we had a new song called "Sakura Nagashi,
It's really cute again,
It's also very exciting,
It's also fun to listen to.
It's a bit rock-ish.
So it was easy to call out to the audience,
I thought we were performing a new song,
I thought we were performing a new song, but everyone's calls were perfect,
Really?
I was surprised.
I wondered if the song was originally from the original,
It created a great sense of unity,
I thought the song was going to get better and better as we played it.
Will this be released on the 31st?
At 24:00 on the 30th.
Yes, it is.
So please download and listen to it.
Please do.
Tomorrow? Tomorrow.
Tomorrow night?
Tomorrow 10 midnight.
It's the end of May already.
That's awful, isn't it?
It's so early.
Well, that's how it's going to be.
We'll have 8 or 7 members this time,
The formation, the singing, the choreography, etc. have all changed,
The choreography and everything has changed.
Many things have changed.
We all worked together to make it happen.
What do you think?
But what do you think?
I've been working on it since Ayaka's Anation,
I've been with Aline and others,
I've been with Aline and other Namie members,
I've been with Namie for a long time.
Until now,
I used to be able to see you once a month or so,
We don't get to see each other. We used to say that it was hard to see each other,
I used to say it was hard to see you,
But this period of time has been great, hasn't it?
Yes, it was.
It's not often you get to see Arin this much, is it?
No, it's not.
That's why,
We've always been good friends,
But we got to know each other even better than usual,
In the beginning, when we were MC'ing, it was like you were the only one talking,
In the beginning, when we were doing MC, it seemed like only Arin was speaking.
But now everyone can talk.
It was like we could talk and have a good time.
It was amazing. Namie's MC.
After Arin said something,
Everyone talks at the same time.
I can't stop talking.
Who's talking? What's talking?
I thought Arin told you.
No, it's Harima.
Mr. Harima.
Harima, you're the best.
It's amazing, isn't it? The way he talks,
I'm not talking about that.
I'm talking about Harima, too,
Even Harima's voice is so loud that it sounds as if he is talking in a shu.
I was surprised.
They sent me a video of the rehearsal on the day of the show, before the performance,
It was supposed to be all of us singing together,
It was like the voices of Harima and the six of us.
But I understand.
I thought that during rehearsal, too.
Everyone was singing,
Harima's voice is so deep.
Her voice is so loud.
Even though she was wearing a mask,
It was as if only Harima wasn't wearing a mask.
I'm talking about the fact that Harima's voice is really clear.
I'm talking about a mistake.
But everyone was,
They rehearsed at the wrong time,
Like, "Oh!
I didn't do "A".
But..,
That's exactly right,
Ilin also told me that we've been getting along well lately,
I told her that we've been getting along well lately,
I was able to get along with Aylin, too.
Ira was really aggressive with her.
Oh, that's scary.Ew, scary.
Arin was crying.
What kind of training do they give you to be so aggressive with your seniors?
I don't know.
Where did you fly the gun?
On Daiei Dori,
"Yume Monogatari",
At the end, when he says hello to J.A., he's facing Aaryn,
I'm facing Aaryn.
I said hello like J.A.
At that moment,
Aaryn was making a sound with a straight face.
Aaryn is so cute.
Was Aaryn crying?
He said Ayla gave him a hard time.
After that, I followed her up with a gunshot.
I chased after him.
That's a role.
Why did you have to chase after her?
It was the encore song of the second part.
But that doesn't mean we had to skip it.
That's not a reason at all.
I wanted to skip it because it was the last song.
You said I could go for it because it was the last minute.
It wasn't a reason at all.
I felt like I could do whatever I wanted.
That's no good.
You have to do it right at the very end.
Encore is a little too much,
I had to know where to stand, how to sing, and so on,
I felt that an encore was a bit more liberating,
Encores seem to me to be more open.
I understand that it is open,
I understand that it is open, but I don't understand why the first thing they do after being opened up is to skip the encore.
And to the senpai.
But I think it was good for MC material.
He said he didn't have much to say.
- Is that what you call promotion?
Not at all. No, not at all.
And it wasn't that exciting,
He talked for less than a minute.
I got blown away. I'm scared. Next up.
Switching poses. Wasn't he great?
I'm so popular.
We finished pretty early, didn't we?
It was fun.
There were a lot of happenings, though.
I'm so sad.
Arin was cute.
I think there will be another show.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm also looking forward to seeing the 7 members of Namie and the shirt union.
I hope you will continue to be interested in us.
I look forward to seeing you again.
And the sashi-iri was delicious.
I received a sashi-iri from Aline's mom.
Sandwiches.
Stylish.
Hamburger steak and chicken.
There was a hamburger steak and chicken with sauce and salt.
It was delicious.
We had a break and then had lunch.
I got a lot of compliments from everyone.
It was a sandwich with a lot of lettuce.
It looked a little healthy. And it was chicken.
It's healthy. Is this okay?
What are you talking about? After this.
You can have lunch, too.
I'll eat my lunch, too.
And macaroon ice cream.
And some Tofur.
Tofur was delicious.
And pudding.
I didn't eat it.
That sucks.
It was good.
Tofur.
Sorry, it's okay.
I'm usually very quick with convenience store deliveries.
They knew. Something was written about me.
I don't know, something on, what was it, Twitter? Instagram?
No, I didn't look at Twitter.
Did they send me a message?
Insta?
I posted a picture of some food I brought for her, and she responded to it,
I saw a staff member buying a bunch of stuff at a convenience store.
I thought, "I didn't ask them to buy this, but they bought everything,
I was not buying a bag, but an eco-bag,
I brought not a bag but an eco-bag, and the eco-bag was so packed that it was a lot of stuff.
Thank you, I'm so happy. I'm sure you'll be very happy to hear that, though.
You guys must have eaten most of the food, right?
Yes, we did. We asked for it.
Yes, we did. I want it.
If they know that, they'll miss it.
You haven't eaten much?
I didn't eat much. My schedule was pretty tight, so I didn't eat much.
That's right.
I didn't eat much.I couldn't eat much.
Yuko ate a lot of pineapple.
Fruit, fruit, fruit.
Did you have fruit?
They always buy fruit for us.
I requested it. And he bought a lot of fruit,
Pineapples, apples, and even watermelons.
I had never seen watermelon before, but it was sold at a convenience store.
There were so many.
You ate a lot of fruits, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
Well, there were a lot of gifts, and it was a lot of fun.
I even had malosi once.
Maroshi?
Don't you know Maloshi gummies? They are very tasty.
You can find them in convenience stores?
Yes, they do. I recommend you to try them if they are the best gummi.
If you like those squishy gummies, I highly recommend them.
They are delicious.
It's hard like Haribo, isn't it?
No, it's not.
It's the exact opposite.
It's really more like a marshmallow.
No, no, no. I'm not talking about food.
Yes, it is.
It's not.
I'm off the hook, though.
I also got it from Aylin's mother,
It was fun to go to the beach. That's what I was talking about.
Thank you very much.
It was a lot of fun.
It was such a great time at Namihe,
Amefurashi has many more gigs coming up,
So I'd like to start the announcement time.
Announcement time.
First of all, I'd like to announce something new, or rather, something that just came out a few days ago,
It just came out the other day.
We will be playing at a festival called "Spark" on July 15 at Lake Yamanaka,
Spark festival, which will be held on July 15 at Lake Yamanaka.
Yay!
Lake Yamanaka.
Yamanashi prefecture.
We will perform on July 15.
Tickets are on sale until 23:59 on May 31.
If you are close by, or if you are interested in directing with us, please let us know,
If you are close by, or if you are interested in directing the show with us, please let us know.
Next, who is it?
Who is this? Is this me?
No, it's not.
Well, go ahead.
Okay, Yuzu.
Yes, I will be appearing at Shake Up Up tomorrow.
Tomorrow, the benefit will be held in the middle of the day,
It is the Aiai Umbrella benefit event.
Let's take Aiai Umbrella Chickie and other pictures with Yuki.
And on June 3, I will be performing at Yuzu Kids Fair Fest.
Iiiiiiiiiiii.
You've been rehearsing, haven't you?
I've been rehearsing. Has it been a while? That activity.
The live concert in Ameura is not a rehab, right?
Yes, it has been a long time. It's been a long time since we've had a video for use, so I'd like to do my best for everyone, but we will be performing in the second part.
We are going to perform in the second part.
It's been two years.
That's amazing. I'm surprised.
I was so happy that Yuzuki-chan called us. I was happy that Yuzuki-chan invited me.
Thank you very much.
I'll make it a lot more exciting.
Yes, I will. I will do my best to make it exciting. Please look forward to it.
Yes, I will. Is this it?
This is the open recording event for the program on June 10.
We are doing a radio show called "Ameura Night" in Ameura City,
We are going to have an open recording of the program on June 10.
There will be two parts to this event.
There will be one part and two parts, but the first-come, first-served general admission starts on June 2,
Please don't forget to come.
Please don't forget. Please do not forget about it.
Next.
Oh, you did that?
We are actually holding the release right now, and there are only 3 left.
That's fast.
The next one is on Sunday, June 4. It will be held at Raraport Tachikawa Tatehi.
That's next week.
Yes, there will be one from 1pm and one from 4pm.
Newcomers can take two-shot for free and watch the live performance for free,
Anyone can watch, so please bring lots of people.
I really want you to come. I really want you to come.
On Sunday, June 11, we will be at Aeon Mall Tokoname in
Nagoya.
Expedition.
Aichi.
There will be an event starting at 12:00.
We are going to perform at a festival on that day,
We are going to perform at a festival called Mist Fest.
Yes, on the 11th.
On the 11th.
We will be playing at Lily Bae 5,
I don't know. It might be Mai.I don't know. Maybe it's Mai.
It's definitely 5.
Mai?
How early in the morning did you come?
He said we should do all the sightseeing after that.
Okay, first thing.
What? I don't need that information.
You won't understand.
The festival is coming up after Lilybae in Tokoname.
Please check it out.
The last day is Saturday, June 24th.
We will be at 7 ports and FES.
The time for this one is still on the schedule,
We will try to let you know as soon as possible.
We are aiming for a final attendance of 500 people,
If you would like to join us, we would be happy to have you as an acquaintance,
If you are interested, please bring someone you know, or even someone you know who is not your friend.
Even Yotomo.
Or maybe you've seen that girl before.
Is your friend cool?
Do you have a Yotsuya?
We are looking forward to seeing 500 people at Laraport on June 24th.
Please help us out.
It's almost useless.
I'll be waiting.
And last but not least,
July 9th in Shinjuku,
We Amefurassi's one-man live performance,
Bayusai 2023 is scheduled for July 9 in Shinjuku.
The date is getting closer and closer,
Tickets are now on sale,
There will be two parts, one for the first and one for the second,
Both parts will be completely different from each other,
We are aiming for a sold-out show for both,
Tickets are selling well,
The fans told me that the venue is easy to see even if you're at the back of the line,
The information from fans' boobs.
So I think it's true.
I hope you will come to the Amefurashi's one-man show.
Please do.
Tickets are on sale now.
I'll be waiting for you.
Okay, can I parture?
Please do.
Mr. YTX Pet Tail Feelings.
Sorry for the typo.
I hope you are healthy and active in mind and body.
Thank you very much.
Not at all.
We just didn't stop.
Mr. Sadaaki.
Blow Your Mind 250,000 views is amazing.
I'm looking forward to seeing how far it will go.
I'm happy.
If today's Sweat had 240,000 views or something like that, if it grows even 10,000 views.
That's right.
The Blow Your Mind music video has surpassed 250,000 views.
Thank you very much.
That's the first time it's gotten over 200,000 views.
You know I met the director who shot it the other day.
Everyone was so happy.
It's amazing, isn't it?
I'm very grateful.
You filmed in Taiwan, right?
You were talking about the Taiwan episode last week.
You weren't there.
I'm watching something interesting.
If it's your first time, that's great.
I talk about it every week in the field.
It's much more interesting.
Especially, the good and the bad players got together and got excited.
The good and the bad are getting excited.
It's interesting that they don't get into it.
We think it's interesting, too.
Well, well, well.
Just listen to me.
How long are you going to give me my glasses back?
And this is getting like that.
It's going like this.
It's not in there at all.
Doesn't it make you feel uncomfortable? When you wear glasses.
It's just my imagination.
My head hurts.
It's like this.
Before I went to Taiwan, when I was going from Japan to Taiwan,
I was at the airport on the Japanese side,
You know those machines that you have to go through for the physical examination?
You know the one where you have to go through a machine to check your status?
If they say "OK," you can go,
When we were all standing in line, there was a huge breeze coming out of the machine,
It was like Nishikawa-san's TM debut,
Like fairies.
It was my turn, so I went first.
I did it like this, the moment the wind came,
I said, "The fairies,
I went toward Hana and Yuzu, and Yuzu and Hana were getting excited together,
The attendant asked me, "Why aren't you moving? Are you bright red?
I was so angry with him in a serious tone,
I felt like I was bothering him.
He didn't laugh?
He didn't laugh at me.They didn't laugh at me.
No thanks, Yuzuka too, eeeeee! Yui! Yui! Like that.
Aira was on stage all by herself,
Then, they don't get excited on stage, do they?
Aira would do it everywhere as if it was her own stage,
It's the worst.
This episode is not interesting unless you get excited together.
When they get out of the lecture, they do things like eating ramen noodles,
That's how they get excited.
I'm not doing it. I'm not doing it.
I'm doing it because I'm hungry.
That's what I'm doing.
I'm doing it alone, where no one is watching.
Every time I'm in a groove, when I'm on a plane,
I'm in economy and business class,
I do it every time,
I do it every time.
This way, right?
Every time. I'm sure they do it.
It's not funny,
It's not funny at all.
Just as I was about to do it, the couple in front of me was doing it, too, and it was a little awkward.
We were in the same boat.
I mean, no?
I mean, the T-game repositioning thing, too,
I mean, I knew that the person who was doing it was the one who was doing it.
I'm sure that's true.
Here we go again.
It's so annoying.
He looked so cold.
Please don't move.
I really thought she might giggle a little,
But he didn't smile at all,
It was really awkward.
That's why I was on the second floor.
After that, the sight of Aira being awkward was too funny,
We laughed so hard over there.
The two of us.
We were like, "Coo-coo," and we were both like, "Oh, my God!
We were in different lanes at that time.
Aira was super excited.
No, it's too loud.
It was fine.
Yuzu and Hana were dancing to Aira, which is rare.
Okey-dokey.
They got mad at me all by themselves.
That's nice. That was fun.
There's one more thing. That kind of similar episode.
Yeah, something like that.
We flew on a plane, a SeaWheel plane,
We flew from Taiwan to Japan.
There are tens of thousands of things to do on an airplane, right? Basically.
You can't even play with your phone.
We were all making funny faces.
We took pictures of them, and we were all asking ourselves how we could do it, how we could get the angle right.
It wasn't a funny face contest without any work to do.
It was already, like, can I take an ugly picture?
At that very moment, who can make the chin tuck the most, like a mountain.
Because I can make it straight.
I can do it quickly.
I can do it beautifully.
The squatting championship.
That's right.
We had a great one.
It was pretty exciting, and we all had a lot of fun, and the angle was pretty good.
We were all doing it together.
All four of us were doing it together?
Yeah, yeah.
We took pictures of each person and said, "Yuzu, just try it.
We lined up the four of us.
You mean you have a picture?
No, I don't.
There are pictures, aren't there?
I really don't want to do this.
I'm sorry, I really shouldn't do that," said Mr. Suzuki, who was the least likely to do it.
Was the child still pretending to be cute?
I wasn't trying to be cute,
Haneda, you're so good.
I'm good.
I'm good at it because I have a sharp chin.
Because I'm sharp.
I'm super funny.
While I was playing with it, a CA came over and our eyes met just as Haneda was doing it,
It was awkward.
He looked really awkward.
He was very noisy.
He also kept a funny face.
It was fun, wasn't it?
It wasn't a silly time, it was fun.
It was fun.
That's what we were talking about.
It was the most fun to be silly, wasn't it?
The fire is quick to flare up because it shakes so fast.
You're close, aren't you?
I think I'll be photographed someday. I make a lot of funny faces outside.
I don't make funny faces when I'm walking home from lessons.
I make funny faces.
I'm making funny faces.
I'll take a picture of me on the train, like I'm on the train, here, and send it to my teeth.
Seriously.Seriously.
Yuzu's is the worst.
Yuzu is really bad.
He makes such a funny face.
I make a funny face and send a picture of it on the train.
His teeth are still good. I still don't get it.
I still don't get it. If the angle from the bottom still says "funny face".
I'll send you something that looks like a light funny face.
Don't shoot from the bottom. I'm lighting in the middle.
It's really great.
What did people think of me because I took a picture of him making a funny face and sent it to him on the train?
It's not good.
So, every time I take a picture, I use a word for a moment, something like "peen something" in a loud voice.
When everyone comes down and it's not too quiet.
When they are giggling something.
Because that's not where it's supposed to be.
It's great.
You brought the meaning of the heart, took the picture, and did it like this.
Wow, Yuzu.
You're good. I'm learning from you.
I don't take pictures when I take pictures, I just take them here. After that.
Ah, I see.
After that, I don't think you have to work that hard.
He will send you a very high quality picture.
He sends them to me.
I appreciate it.
That's great. That's how you were taking pictures.
I'll be photographed someday, right?
I'm not trying hard enough.
Someday I'll be photographed.
You have two choices.
That funny face.
The funny face on the candy flash train.
Either my funny face will go around, or they will notice that I'm carrying a lot of gifts back home.
That's right.
I'm sure it will show up someday.
I just want everyone to keep that in mind.
What do you mean?
I really think it's going to happen.
If Hana's cell phone gets leaked, it's really bad.
It's bad, it's really bad.
It's really bad.
Please don't lose your cell phones.
But he has almost no pictures. Delete them.
The old, bad one. The old, bad one of the Corona Disaster.
The Corona Disaster is pretty bad for your bijou, too, since you're in bed all the time.
You're the only one who stays in bed all the time.
What? I know, everyone says that.
Also, you know, when you get quarantined,
It's a lockdown.
I know, I know.
When someone gets coronated,
You can't go back and forth between rooms, so you have to stay in your room the whole time.
When the symptoms come on.
Yes, and at that time, too.
The bijuju is very bad in the bosagas.
But I want to make funny faces.
When I see this bijou, I want to make a funny face.
What?
You are so timid.
I'm getting really timid.
I'm serious.
Really timid.
I can't tell you that I can't show you,
What's the word? I can say it, but I can't.
I want to show it, but I can't. I really can't.
It's so funny. It's really funny.
I mean, how can you make a face like that? It's like, "How can you do that?
I'm doing this too. I thought to myself.
The flowers were pretty amazing too.
Flowers are pretty amazing, too,
But he also sent me flowers sometimes.
The impact of the flowers was beyond impressive.
Really.
It's really funny.
What's with the competitive spirit?
It's not that I'm competitive, it's just that everyone is half-hearted.
They're trying their best. I'm giving it my all. I'm giving it my all.
Let's go to the bathroom and stand in front of the mirror,
How far to the left can I go?
I'm sure you'll look very different.
It's different, isn't it?
I was with Hana and she was throwing up on my arm in the cab.
I was wearing a mask when I was paired with Hana,
We were both doing it automatically,
We were both wearing masks, and we were trying to see how long we could make the blank space of the mask
We were sending each other messages.
We were sending pictures to each other.
We took pictures together and sent them to Yuzu.
I wondered how they did it.
It was amazing.
We're looking at the front and back together, like a frilly thing.
As an air-phone.
Yuzu didn't even see it because it was sent by the two of us.
Like this.
Really, after we were sent too.
After Yuzu's really long one was sent to us.
I wondered how we could do it.
We both did it.
But I really can't do it.But I really can't.
Oh man, I want to see it.
Maybe I'll do it at the Ameeture.
No, I can't.
It's a broadcast accident.
You still think it's something you can show, don't you?
It's really no good.
It's true.
I'll only show it to Shi-chan once.
Just one picture.
When you get to this level and you understand.
I don't think she'll see it unless I show it to her.
I didn't write the address.
The confidence one.
The address.
I can't see anything because it's shhhh.
It wasn't that bad, was it?
The whole thing is interesting.
Don't mention the details.
There are so many different ones, I don't know.
It will take time.
I don't know if I can make it into a project.
I can't do it.
It's absolutely impossible.
The manager will give me an NG.
It's a NG.
It's really bad.
But still, I'm doing it in front of people.
Oh no, 580 people are watching, right now.
Wow. That's amazing.
You're doing it in a cab or on a train, right?
Cab? You're out, right?
You're taking a cab. Or on a plane.
But I thought it was okay since we only met once.
If I had done it here, it would have already made the rounds.
I just did it there. It's going to be circulated.
In that case. It's a moment that burns in your eyes.
Yes, yes, yes.
Whether the person blurts it out or not.
And if it is shown to a stranger, you will only meet that person once.
That's how it is. I see.
That's the end of it.
I'm talking about something really unimportant.
Isn't it really humid?
It's terrible. My hair is spreading so much.
But I've been wanting to fix my bangs since a while ago.
You've been doing it for a long time.
The bottom part of your hair isn't a mirror anymore.
You've been grinning at me for a while now.
Can I read it? Can I read it?
Spachan Star? Can I show you some more?
Yes, you can.
It's from Peach Shrimp.
From Momoebi Alas.
I really want to go to your one-man show, but my schedule doesn't allow me to go, so I'm supporting you from Kyushu.
I will definitely come to see you when you come to Kyushu on tour or something.
It is going to get hotter and hotter from now on, so please take care of yourself and do your best.
Thank you very much.
Also, who commented to me earlier that they had never seen me before.
Thank you, Tomo Tart. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. I'm so glad.
Even though it's your first time, you gave us a spachan.
I'm glad.
It was pretty good.
The face might be normal.
There are worse ones.
You'd think they'd be okay with that.
I'm not going to let you get in the way of that.
It's no good.
Eeeee!
One more time, one more time.
There are worse ones.
I'm sorry. Good luck with your imagination, everyone.
It was more than I imagined.
It's even worse than this.
Sure, this might be normal.
Not at all.
There are worse.
It's hard to believe that this face is doing it.
Because it's really more than I imagined.
It's like that.
About 100 times more than the funny faces we make in front of everyone.
I see.
I'm having fun with such nonsense.
I think it means that we, Amefurashi, are at peace, laughing at trivial things.
We are really peaceful.
It's not good. There are only 20 minutes left.
The music video has 250,000 views.
Thank you very much.
It's getting a lot of buzz.
I think there may be some people who are watching this stream for the first time today.
It's true that it was triggered by something.
That's right.
But, do you ever feel that we are not getting enough buzz lately?
Do you hear that from the people who are getting the most buzz?
By the way, you are the person who receives the most money.
Do you listen to the people who get the most buzz?
Good sense.A good feeling.
Meaning?
It means that we are getting the most out of it.
And the most important thing is that we get the most buzz.
Do you mean especially the good ones or the bad ones?
Only the good ones.
Only the bad ones.
So, you don't have that with the good ones?
She's the first one to get the buzz.
But then Aiara came along and got my attention.
It became a "super erase".
Shimote-super-erase.
That's not what I meant, but I think we are becoming more well-known as a group.
I felt it more and more.
Like going to idol festivals,
Some of the people you meet tell you that they saw you on TikTok.
That's right.
That's what I wanted to talk about.
I see.
Is there? I'm really feeling it.
Boo-boo. But I've heard from the members that it's not me, it's not who I am, it's not me.
I was approached by Hazama and Hana-chan on the street, and before I went to the lesson, I realized that I was a character even though I was spinning, so I said "booboo.
I'm not a character, I'm a spinner, but I'm a character, I'm a spinner, I'm a spinner, I'm a character, I'm a spinner.
I'm just saying that it's a bit of a bother if it's too much, but I'd really like to have my lesson alive and running as fast as I can, even if I'm running late.
I was running as fast as I could even though I was running late, and she looked at me like I was weird, and I wondered why, but she was really cute.
Then he said that he was going to do Amehei after that, and that he was going to do Amehei.
I was running as fast as I could with my boss exposed, and I was wearing a pin, and I was dirty...
I was in pain, but I told him I was, and he said congratulations!
I'm glad to hear that.
I was also approached by people who said, "I'm going to a meeting, please do your best!
They were so cute in their love clothes, they would know I was wearing a kersh.
I'm so happy to be called by you.
I'd love to be approached.
That's true.
In the city, it's a bit more relaxed.
I think it's a little bit of a common sense thing to do.
When I'm with the other members, I'm very happy to be called by them.
But I'm sorry that we look like a salt tie when we're not wearing any clothes, because I don't want to show you that I look like a salt tie.
I'm sorry for being so selfish. I really am. I'm glad to be approached, though.
If you see me, please say hi. I've had 10,000 instagrams for a while.
Yes, I have 10,000 followers on Instagram.
I'm glad to hear that. I'm glad to hear that you're promoting Ilan too.
I'm glad to hear that.
I'm very happy, I'm very happy.
I'm very happy.
But I was so close to getting it.
So I was saying on insta-live that I wanted to reach 10,000 by summer, in July or so,
But it happened a lot faster than that,
That was amazing.
I was really surprised.
I'm very happy to see 10,000 people.
It's fun.
It's like I don't know what "1" is.
I've been longing for this for a long time.
I was so happy at that moment.
Everyone was so happy, and the fans were so happy too.
Ten thousand people is a strange feeling.
I was so happy.
Thank you very much.
Why? I think Spacha's a little...
Oh, yes!
AO's and MEIYAN's spacha had disappeared a little...
Thank you for sending it to me!
Sorry, I couldn't read it.
Thank you.
We are very happy to see the buzz on our site.
I hope you guys will continue to spread the word about us,
Thank you so much for spreading the word and putting it on TikTok.
Thank you so much, it's going to come around a lot.
I hear it really does come around.
A lot.
Hari-chan and the others, 3 out of 5 of them seem to be candy fliers.
She sang a lot.
Yesterday, she said she wanted to go out.
Yes, like Magic of Love and Kantu Star,
He said he wanted to teach me a lot of things.
He was cute.
It was cute.
I want to thank you all for your continued support, and thanks to all of you, this buzz has been generated.
Please keep up the good work.
Please continue to support us.
We want you to get to know us better, so we've prepared a new section,
We have prepared a new section that will run four times starting this week.
Wow, this is a big project.
To my surprise, this is the first section.
I'm sorry.
I got carried away. I got excited with my funny face.
There's more to come.
I didn't expect the funny faces.
Okay, I'll start with the second one.
But it's impossible to do that unless I've already played it, so if it takes less than 15 minutes, I'll do the second one.
Sorry. Um, you don't have to come back from Dubai.
I'm totally fine.
But I'm glad you're back home today.
You're waiting for me now.
I didn't call Juicy.
Please wait.Wait a minute.
Can I see this corner one more time? Just in case.
Okay. Okay. Just in case.
Okay, I'll just say the title.
Nice to meet you, I'm Ameflash.
Whether you're a recent acquaintance or a long-time supporter,
We hope that all of you will get to know us better,
We are going to feature each and every member of Ameflash in this in-depth project.
Each week, we'll be highlighting a different member of Ameflash.
That's great, isn't it?
But I'm a little nervous about the idea of "making an example of" you.
Are you okay?
Negative promotion is important this time of year.
I'm fine.
I know what I'm talking about.
Don't worry.
I'm scared.
Don't worry. I won't make a fool of you.
The members have the most at stake.
It won't be a corner for Moka to worry about.
So, who will be the victim to be made an example of today?
It's Moeka Suzuki.
Hey! You idiots.
You make it up as you go along every time.
You idiots! You idiots! You idiots!
And this stupid script! I'm gonna break this stupid script!
Stupid Flash!
Shabo.
I have a script after this.
I can't tear it up.
There's a script after this.
A script-reading queen is the kind of thing that connects with the heart.
That's right. You can't tear it up.
I don't need this.
I don't need the one I've already read.
Can I tear this one?
This one is important.
That was beautiful. Thank you very much for the kiregami. Thank you again today.
You're really good. Really.
It's like I'm playing a flat character, though,
But you can see the gap between the two, and it's quite nice to see the sharpness of the game.
I can't do it myself. This potential is amazing.
It's amazing. I can't believe your acting ability.
When Ai and the others do it, it's just the same as usual.
I like the gap between the two.
I think she's a good actress.
If it was the same as usual, I would have fallen for it.
I'm a little caught up.
These girls are all fake.
The real me is the one who is cute, can sing well, and heals everyone with her best smile and smiling power.
It's up to you whether you believe this or not.
Believe it.
Really?
Now that this farce is over, I would like to get down to business.
This time, I would like to feature MOEKA and tell you the charm of MOEKA.
Best regards.
I've been thinking about it for a long time.
I think that MOEKA has always featured members in the past.
Is it because I am older?
Because I am the oldest.
Why is that?
I would like to try MOEKA.
Why?
Because MOEKA is the safest place.
But I've done individual projects before and probably haven't even made it to the nose yet.
Is that so?
I haven't reached the top of my previous project and I haven't reached the top of my previous project.
Maybe it's MOEKA.
Maybe I don't even have to do it.
I'm always the only one who doesn't do it.
It always ends with one or two people.
I want to do my best this time and finish the project.
So, MOEKA, the first one is the most important.
Yes, I will.
Please do your best.
Well, once again, it's nice to meet you, I am MOEKA Suzuki.
Yes, I'm MOEKA Suzuki. I am MOEKA Suzuki.
I was born on February 5th, Nikoniko Day, and I am 21 years old now.
And I am Seizawa Mizugame.
Everyone envies me quite a bit.
He is cute.
It's kind of cute when you make it into a character.
There are a lot of cute ones, aren't there? Water turtles.
I guess I have that kind of background because I am cute.
I am also left-handed.
When I say that I am left-handed, I am often told by my fans that I am a genius or something.
But the left-handed person is a genius, and that has already happened a long time ago.
Please stop it. I'm just a left-handed person.
I am just a left-handed person.
I'm just a left-handed person.
I haven't checked your blood type yet.
Maybe A?
Definitely not A.
I think it's AO.
I've been told I'm an A type by some members, but my friends say I'm more like an O type.
I don't know why.
But there is an O element in me.
Yes, I do. I also have an "O" element.
Oops, is it both?
Maybe this is O.Maybe this is an O.
This O that you can see in this A-like little place is pretty much an O constitution, isn't it?
It's like an "O" with a strong "A".
But who's the member I don't know yet?
I don't know.
I'm either an A or an O.
By comparison.
Hana is definitely an A.
Which one is Hana?
Am-chan, A?
I don't know yet. Which is it?
My favorite food is chocolate and milk.
I love them by themselves, and I even love them in combination.
All I eat is chocolate.
I know. I really want to stop it somehow.
I was told yesterday, "You don't have any chocolate. He said he didn't have any chocolate.
I took one of Yuzu's precious chocolates from her before I took it out.
But I didn't take it.
I was patient.
I held back and asked the staff to take it.
I didn't hold back or anything.
On the contrary, I ate it.
I didn't take one of the chirori chocolates.
I didn't take it.
You eat chocolate while taking a bath, right?
Yeah.
I like the way it melts a little bit.
I love it. Anyway, chocolate and milk.
I also usually play acoustic guitar and distribute my music.
I also have another hobby that I recently discovered.
What is it? We haven't mentioned it?
Yes, we have.
What?
My hobby is to untangle tangled necklaces.
So if you find a tangled necklace, you're supposed to deliver it to me.
Bracelets or necklaces.
You know, that string.
It is Aira who often gets them tangled.
Aiara says, "I want to do it.
Lately, she wants to do it.
She wants to do it.
He uses it from the top.
I want to do it.
I want to do it. Let me do it. I want to do it.
It's fun. That feeling. It's like a circle of wisdom.
You don't like the circle of wisdom?
I don't like the Wheel of Wisdom.
There was one.
You like the details, don't you?
Yes, it is. It's fun. That's your hobby.
Yes, it is. Also, my personality is indecisive.
I'm the oldest, but I rely on everyone in the group.
Please take care of me.
That's right.
That's all.
How about this? Go ahead... the simplest, simplest version.
I don't care if you speak English or not, and obviously, water is a prominent part of it, so what's the point?
I don't know, maybe some people don't know that I'm left-handed, but I don't know which way to look at it. It's like...
I'd like to know what kind of character you are, or what kind of person you'd be good for, or something like that.
If you want to be healed, I'm here to help you. Are you healed?
Yes, I think I have a smile on my face.
Can I try it as a client?
No way!
Perks.
Yes, as a guest.
Okay, next one, please.
Thank you very much.
I can't shake hands.
Well, can I kiss you?
No, I can't.
You didn't heal me.
I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine.
You should be able to do that.
If you don't kiss me, I won't be healed, so I'm leaving.
On the contrary.
I'll leave.
I don't want you to come.
Don't come.
What's so comforting about this?
This is soothing.
You've got a face like this all over the place.
I'll be healed.
Oh, I'll tell you what.
No, no, no, why do you think you can kiss me?
I just wanted to be healed.
That sucks.
I just wanted some warmth.
They call me Dequin.
Dequin.
I've never been here before.
Oh, my God.
I didn't know... you're not supposed to do that.
I didn't know that.
You don't have to think about it.
It's not every day you get to meet an idol that you can kiss.
I learned a lot from you.
Thank you very much.
You're right about YouTube.
I've been on YouTube for a long time.
I mean, it's YouTube.I mean, it's YouTube.
It's easy to say anything, and there's a lot of it.
Yes, it is.
I hate it.
I think it doesn't matter.
It's not like it's YouTube. It's whatever.
Yeah.
This girl is amazing.
If she doesn't like one or the other, she'll go with this one.
I don't care about either one.
As long as you don't mind.
She's fine with either one.
It doesn't matter where we go for dinner.
It doesn't matter.
You don't complain about where you go because you've made a decision.
No, I don't.
I don't complain.
I don't.
For example, yesterday at the wave.
I was deciding which hairpiece I liked better.
I was trying to decide... which hairstyle I wanted.
Yuzu's hair ornament.
I'm sure this one will look better with the hair like this.
I said, "This one.
I said, "Thank you, I'll do that.
I'm glad you like it.
I don't care which one you choose.
As long as it's cute.
It's okay.
Then I'll do it this way.
If you get a good reaction...
I'd be happy.
I'm fine either way.
I'm just saying.
I'm sure she's fine either way.
Me too.
When we were talking about going out to eat with Moka.
When we were talking about what we'd like...
Moka said she's fine with anything.
I like everything, so anything is fine.
I wanted to know what you like.
I wanted to know what you like these days.
I've been asking her in a roundabout way.
I've been asking in a roundabout way.
I want to know, but I don't know.
It's kind of frustrating.
I thought that if I asked you directly.
I thought it's a little late for that.
It's true...
You're so soft and pliable, Nao.
When it comes to deciding between Moana and dinner...
She really can't make up her mind.
Hana doesn't care what it's for.
As long as it tastes good.
Someone please decide.
You decide?
Do you have a decision?
Aira said she'd go before.
But she had to go to the salon.
She went home... and Izu and Hana...
Hana?
I want Hana.
I like Hana.
Hana, Yuzu and Moeka...
"Let's go out to eat.
They're both so excited to see me
Like it's a given.
Like it's a given that they'll decide on dinner.
I said, "What are we going to eat?
There's no way you two can decide.
Yuzu should decide.
There's no way we can decide.
Maybe it's because we don't decide.
Maybe it's because we don't decide as a matter of course.
It doesn't matter what we do.
That's the thing.
I'd like to decide somehow.
It really doesn't matter.
Really, anything.
I mean, in a good way. Anything.
I don't mean whatever you want.
Because I want you to come with that stance.
If that's the case.
I'm happy with any of it.
Meat, fish, Chinese...
I'm happy with anything.
If you tell me which one you'd like.
I'd be happy to.
We both have low voices, and we're both very calm.
I'm comfortable with anything.
I don't care what your stance is.
From our point of view.
I don't care what it is.
If we decide to do it this way...
Okay, let's go.
No, no, no.
Thank you... for deciding.
Let's go.
Let's go
Let's go.Let's go
I was doing "let's go".
Different music.
Let's go
That's funny.
I'm still practicing.
Well, let's try that now.
Come to Misink.
All of you.
We're done with the mini-house.
Hey, guys.
It's a good time. Wanna go out for dinner?
I'm sorry, why am I at the hairdresser's?
Who's that?
That's the accountant.
Sorry, sorry.
It's written down.
You want to take a look and decide?
They all look delicious.
Which one do you want and what do you want to eat?
Whatever you want.
There's no way we can decide.
Are you sure you don't mind?
Even meat.
Fish.
Anything.
I'd love that.
Okay, then. This beef tongue.
Or this omelet with rice.
But I dare you.
If it's a dare, I'll make a pot with everyone.
I'll give you three choices.
Anything is fine.
Anything.
It's a little bit cold today.
It's winter and it's getting cold.
Anyway, I'll make a nabe.
Good night.
Teletele, teletele, teletele.
Is this how you want it?
I'm so happy with this.
Let's try something like this.
I'm already satisfied with this.
I don't feel guilty
I don't feel guilty.
Let's try this one.
That's a good point.
I'll do that next time.
Thank you very much.
And so...
Suzuki, Moya-san's
The end?
What do we do now?
Which one do you like?
First Impressions
I'm curious about this.
There's such a thing as first impressions.
I'd like to hear this.
First of all...
You want me to guess?
When we...
When we first saw you.
What did you think?
I'll ask you to guess.
Okay.
I'll do the writing and I'll do the writing.
I wonder...
What?
Do you remember?
How many years ago? It was...
Let's see, like nine years ago.
How long have you been together?
Nine years.
You've been together for nine years?
And it will be 10 years in November.
Really?
Ten years.
Ten years this year.
We started dating.
You're getting married?
We're getting married.
Isn't 10 years too long?
I've never heard that they've been together for 10 years.
We've been together 10 years at a time.
Do you remember the first day we met?
I remember the atmosphere.
It was like we were singing one by one.
I hate it.
To determine classes A through D,
To divide the ABCD classes,
One by one at the hinagami.
They sang one by one. It's kind of a win-win face-off.
Maybe you think you don't know some people,
Before Ameglas, there was a big group called 3BJr.
We were a group of about 26 people.
We were a group of about 26 people, and now we are down to four,We were a group and now there are four of us,
I would like to know the process.
There are a lot of processes.
We are too large a group, even among the 26 of us.
We were divided into other groups as well.
There was a group within 3BJr.
That group debuted,
Some of them left the 3BJr. group, and some of them chose to graduate,
Some of them left the 3BJr. group, some of them chose to graduate, and some of them left the 3BJr. group,
So there were four of you.
Yes, that's right.
It was 9 years ago, so I don't remember much.
And the first day was in front of a huge group of people, one by one,
There were kids I had almost never met before, so I had to sing by myself in front of them.
There were a lot of adults there,
We were in elementary school and junior high at the time,
I really didn't like it.
We were all in elementary school, right?
My fifth and sixth graders.
They were all in elementary school.
I have nothing but really bad memories.
I can't remember a single thing.
What was your first impression of them that you remember?
Of all the things I remember.
I remember Hana.
I remember Ayanan, too.
Let's have a look.
Ta-da!
You mean Hana thought it was...
That it's a meeting of the four of us?
What do you think Moeka thinks of our first impression of her?
Huh?
Then!
Aira.
What everyone thinks of Moeka.
Aiara thought Moeka was a quiet girl.
And Hana thought she didn't remember.
Yuka is a potato.
Oh, she's like a potato.
I think they thought she was sweet potato.
What do you think?
What's the right answer?
I'll go first.
Actually, I don't remember.
I don't remember at all,
I don't remember it at all,
I think it's the earliest memory I have of Moeka,
I think,
But it's very recent.
What?
Recently?
She asked me for advice once,
What?
We used to have group discussions.
You don't remember that?
What?
Which group?
What group?
Don't you remember before we formed that group?
It was called MAJESTIC 7.
There were several more groups among the three of us.
MAJESTIC 7 was a group that all three of us were in, except for me,
We often had discussions.
Moka couldn't speak up much there,
And Moka, Moka couldn't say much,
And when I did speak up, she would paraphrase me,
So she asked me what she should do.
What?
Oh no.
That's my first impression.
No, I think there's more to it than that.
What I remember most is my memory.
Japan.
No, but you mentioned it.
But it was very recently.
You used to say that.
From the time of Mitsukoshida.
I don't remember if he said it to Hana.
No, but it's different.
Hana and Moeka were the ones who didn't talk.
That's why we didn't talk to each other, so it was a one-handed affair.
There were so many strong-willed girls.
The way you said it.
In a good way, in a good way.
I'm really sorry. I didn't mean it that way.
The ones who are assertive.
A noisy girl.
A girl who can speak her mind.
You didn't mean it that way.
I didn't mean it that way.
At any rate, I have an image of her as a serious girl.
Maybe that's what they say.
After the concert, how did you feel about the staff?
After the concert, I would ask the staff how it went.
She seems like a very serious girl.
That's true.
I also had an image of her as a girl who cries a lot.
Oh, really?
Why was she crying?
She cried a lot.You cried easily.
I had an image of you crying right away.
But seriously, the video too...
But every time I would talk, I would rattle off a laugh.
It was good, and I cried every time I did maman.
That's right.
When I go out on stage, I'm so happy that I cry.
I really do.
We had a rule that I would try not to cry.
It was impossible, because I cried every time I went out on stage.
I have an image of being scolded.
I don't know why I don't cry.
I would cry just to answer the door.
How about now?
Now...
You cry.
Oh, no. Even worse. I really don't like it.
Do you still cry?
I cry a lot.
I understand. I understand a lot.
Don't you know what I mean? You start crying all of a sudden.
Is there any way to get rid of it?
But I'm afraid of crying.
We warned each other about crying during MJ.
It was a really bad thing.
There was a culture.
From Yuzu's point of view, it's like a club activity.
If you cry, they get angry.
Even if you want to cry, you can't cry.
The culture of 3DV's extracurricular activities has become ingrained in our bodies, hasn't it?
I was pretty angry with Maji, so I cry a lot.
I'm afraid it's so ingrained in me that I still can't cry.
I probably don't cry as much as I used to.
When I'm at home or something, I used to be pretty...
I'm pretty dark when I'm at home, so maybe don't tell me.
You can't cry when you're at home.
That's good.
I was surprised to hear you talk about your past.
I used to cry by myself everyday,
But now, when I feel like crying, I can be free of it.
It might be awkward now if I say that I feel like that.
So I'll tell you what you should do.
Thank you.
When I feel like crying during a live performance, I become nothing.
If I start to do it on my own,
Momoka, please think that I'm about to cry.
I see.
I'm so happy to see you here.
When you are happy, cry.
When you are happy, it's fine.
Please do so.
I understand.
Don't be unreasonable.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for the words from the center.
I'm learning a lot.
A lot of things.
Where's Aira?
What about you, by the way?
I don't remember my first impression,
I thought her hair was long.
It is long, isn't it?
I thought it was long.
It was long, wasn't it?
At the time.
It was really long, and I didn't dye it in the first place,
It was heavy.
It was shaggy.
You had long hair, too.
I didn't have bangs either.
It was still clear.
Bangs, too.
The dryness is due to humidity or something.
It's a frizzy thing.
We haven't talked about it.
It bothers you, doesn't it?
It bothers me a lot.
I told you about my family structure.
Yes, you're right.
I might have an image of your hair.
I didn't pay much attention to it. Not really.
It was definitely shaggy.
Like in the pictures from elementary school,
Why are your bangs so shaggy? I was like, "Why are your bangs so shaggy?
I imagine him with a half up-do and a lot of sweat on his face.
The photo of him as a 3D player is really bad.
They are too shaggy.
To be frank, we thought our hair was too shaggy too.
I think everyone has an image of his hair.
We didn't notice it at all.
Maybe that's what leads to the imo world.
That's true.
What about Rizu?
I knew you thought so.
I honestly don't remember.
You don't remember, do you?
What do you remember from the "Nice to meet you" song?
Hari-chan.
I remember dancing to Mottainai,
And a lot of flowers,
I really thought I was a boy.I really thought it was a boy.
I don't even remember the flowers.
I was in elementary school, so I didn't know that only girls were gathered,
I thought there were also boys.
I was handing the microphone to each of them one by one.
I was handing the microphone to Hana,
I thought, "This cute boy is also doing his best,
I looked at him and said, "Good luck," and handed the microphone to him. I handed the microphone to him with a smile on my face.
Summer festival?
Summer festival.
I thought, "Wow!
It was really in England, so it made a strong impression on me,
I don't remember what I served.
Did you do a Kinari memory show?
It's Shiosai's memory.
Ama-chan's.
Shiosai's memory.
Really, no.
I don't always remember.
But if it is the most distant memory,
I was really in the center.
That's why I remember him speaking much more clearly in the past.
I think people have the image that I speak very softly now,
But your original pronunciation is the type where you speak firmly one by one.
He was very firm.
He also had his own opinions.
At a live performance, I would say, "I'm Mayuka Suzuki!
I'm Mayuka Suzuki! Like, "I'm Mayuka Suzuki!
She said every word in a loud and easy-to-understand voice,
During the live performance, I had an image of her as the center of MJ, so I had an image of her being sparkling.
She is so bright and shiny.
He was more confident in himself in the past.
You are sparkling. When I watch old videos.
Morikawa thinks so too.
"Love! I love it! I love it!
There are people who are going to come and see the show.
When I watch old videos, it's like a sparkle that I have confidence in myself.
I often watch Japanese live videos.
Their voices are so sparkling.
They are so idolized.
There is a mixture of freshness. That's...
Lemons are flying around.
It was the most idolized.
It's like lemon squash.
I want to go back.
When was the most recent one?
Tatsuki Tachikawa of Yokogawa.
Fresh name Moeka on June 4.
Yes, something like that.
I want to do my best to be young and energetic.
I think it's not so bad because the adults have settled down, like Hana and the others.
I'm not a woman who smiles a lot, but I'm a woman who doesn't smile.
Protecting. So, I'm sure you've had a chance to get a feel for her.
Meow3
b crystal lotr naa
I'm so glad that the time is over.
I have the bottom script.
I'm from Dubai today, I have to come.
I'll take two, I don't know.
Which one do you want?
What are you torn between right now?
The members introduce themselves! This place is amazing! Suzuki, Mayaka! or Let's thank Moetchan! I'm not sure which one of the two I'm referring to.
I'll try to be thankful, then.
Besides, listen. I thought there would be nothing to be thankful for, that I wouldn't be able to mention it, so I put it at the bottom of the list.
There are about 3, 4, 5, 6, 7 items. I wondered what I wrote at the bottom.
Let's thank Moetchan. I think everyone has various things.
I have one, I have one. I have, I have.
Thank you for pinning it down.
Then, I also have a nose. I have a nose. Okay?
Thank you for ironing it out.
And Yuzu, thanks for always ironing out the elastic.
Okay, that's how we'll do it today.
The members introduce themselves, and here's the best part! Let's do Moya Suzuki.
Okay, Yuzu. I like your kindness in ironing every time and telling me it's ok.
Then, I have one too. I think she is really good at using oil when she sets her hair.
Me too. I think she is very kind when she gives me eyeliner.
Sotto voce.
Maybe I should go home.
I didn't feel motivated at all.
It's the end of the day when I leave now.
Then it's better if we all go home.
There's more to come.
What about you, Daiga?
Well, I'll tell you. Let's be thankful.
I did it.
When we have a discussion or something, I don't talk to him too nicely.
Each member gets depressed at times.
Daiga is the one who sees what's going on the most.
He notices changes in the members,
He doesn't just say, "It's okay" in front of everyone,
He doesn't just say "it's okay" in front of everyone.
He doesn't just say "it's okay," but he stands by you and says, "I know you think like this,
I am grateful for that.
Please support us.
But there are moments when I feel that you are the oldest at your core.
Well, maybe that's why Amefurashi is like this,
It's embarrassing.
It's still embarrassing.
I wonder.
You said you were going to do it before.
No, I don't need it anymore.No, that's enough.
You're starting to embarrass me even though I'm embarrassed.
By the way, who did you really want first and foremost to compliment you a little?
Is that possible?
No, no, I don't know. Was Ira really the right choice?
I just want you to ask me that.
I really want to hear it from someone.
Is that bad?
By the way, was it, uh, was it a little bit like Ira?
Yuzu.
That's a lie. What you just said is a lie. He never did that to me.
One more time. I've never had it done to me again.
They always notice some kind of change, but they don't notice me at all.
They never notice.
They don't notice me at all.
Quite the opposite.
You're saying that a lot, aren't you?
I think they're both cute, so I don't know. There's a difference.
But they don't notice at all.
What changed?
How is it better?
The difference is a little bit of make-up.
Are you satisfied?
Yes, I am.
I don't like it. I'm depressed that I have to do this corner with everyone.
It's my turn too. Because it was my picture.
I don't care if I'm praised.
I'm embarrassed. I'm a little embarrassed.
Then, for this one time only, go to the back.
No, that's why.
I always ended up in the moe car.
I was taking pictures of Moe's car. You shouldn't do that.
I feel like every project ends because of the moe car.
It's your fault that it's the moe car's fault.
So I'm embarrassed to be praised or anything.
I'd stick a QR code on my Instagram for about 10 minutes.
Everyone does it in a different way to promote me.
I see.
I don't want to stop.
I'll do Yuzo next week.
Well, then, next week, please go to Yuzo and think about it.
What are you thinking about in advance?
Oh, man, in a week.
Maybe he'll come up just once.
I guess so.
That's tough.
Thank you very much.
Can I go to the last corner?
Are you okay? Is Dubai okay?
I'm not sure about Dubai, time-wise.
Dubai?
Welcome back. I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I'm sorry, I'm on a tight schedule today.
But I'm staying the night, so you can still come in.
No problem. You can go home.
I still have time to catch my flight.
Please go home.
Are you sure you're okay?
Okay, I'm going. Another week in Suiken.
I'm sorry. Mr. Zusi.
Well, all in this corner of Yuzo's next week.
Please make it a back-row good corner for everyone.
This week, Suicune looked sleepy, so I patted him on the stomach,
I got a very cute Suicune. This is Suicune.
Thank you for watching until the end.
See you next time!
What kind of Suicune?
You haven't shown it to anyone?
I didn't.
You don't look too happy about that, do you? Your face.
It's like, "Oh, no, don't do that.
Shut up. You look super happy.
It hurts a little bit to be counted.
My chest hurts.
You know, before the show started, before the missile started, they showed me a video.
I felt so bad for him.
Why?
It's like a TikTok video, where you press the button, and then they pose you...
It's like, you're on TikTok, and you're pushing and posing.
Was that Suicune?
It was.
I felt so bad for him.
He's so cute, showing his belly like that.
But Suicune was so annoying.
He was smiling at her so much.
Isn't he cute? And then I was like, "I'm sorry, I didn't get my makeup done in time.
So, look at that.
I'm late.
Okay, that's it.
It's been another week of Suicune!
Well, that's why it's almost time for you to go!
Lastly, I'd like to wish everyone a good luck for the week
I'm going to leave you with a good luck spell from Moyaka
Let's say goodbye with Moe Moe Magic Corner!
Thank you for your hard work in May!
Let's work hard in June!
At the end
Hey, hey, hey, hey
Are you trying to end this corner? To this cornerAre you trying to finish this corner? I'm going to finish this corner.
I don't know what to do.
Today was Mayaka's special.
Why don't you continue in front of her with a special version today?
Yes, ma'am.
That was, um...
It's like a prelude.
That's right.
It's a "komi-dashi", right?
Yes, it is.
Oh, oh, I fell.
Me too.
Yes, if you work hard, it's over.
Laughing too much.
Until the rainy season, don't let it rain.
Rain, stop raining.
I think we have a fresh memonker out there, don't you?
Really?
Is it good?
I have high expectations for the 4th.
Yes, look forward to it.
Sparkle.
One of her old specialties was to bend her neck a little and smile after singing.
You used to do that a lot.
I'll give it to you.
Oh, no, I don't.
You might be able to see that.
Yes, you might be able to see it.
If you come on the 4th, you will be able to see a fresh Mayaka, so please look forward to it.
How many years younger will you be?
Uh, about 10 years.
That means?
I will be 10 years old, and 11 years old.
So young.
Much younger.
Young!
You are so young.
You said you were going to see Sushia, who is 11 years old.
Yes, I am.
Please come. Please do.
Please do.
So, let's all go together for the last time.
Seino.
Let it rain while it rains.
Or, in short, rain shame.
Thank you.
See you next week.